ANDRI RAHMAN HAKIM

PROFILE

A full stack web developer (work on both backend and frontend development) which is passionate build various web application, creating seamless user experiences and visually compelling designs for the web, which resonate with audiences and drive engagement.

SKILLS

Programming Language

PHP, Javascript, HTML, CSS, SQL

Framework & Library

• PHP: Laravel, Codelgniter

• Javascript: jQuery, Vuejs

• Theme: Bootstrap, Vuetifyjs, Buefy

Cloud

 Digital Ocean, Netlify, Github Pages, Vercel

TOOLS

- Git, GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket
- Trello, Asana
- Slack, Zoom, Microsoft Teams, Google Meet
- Google Drive, Microsoft Office, Microsoft OneDrive
- Windows, Ubuntu Linux
- VSCode, Notepad++
- PHPMyAdmin, HeidiSQL
- Diagram.net, Canva, Photoshop
- Vim, SSH, Putty, WinSCP

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. Capture Data Teknologi | Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia Senior Web Developer, April 2021 – April 2024

- Guide the team in developing features for the Online
 Assessment Platform, with a focus on boosting user satisfaction and engagement.
- Work together with teams across functions to ensure a consistent brand experience on all platforms.
- Ensure regular maintenance of the server and database to optimize platform performance.

Human Care Consulting | Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia Web Developer, Sept 2020 - April 2021

- Enhancing the Online Assessment Platform's features to elevate user satisfaction and engagement.
- Collaborating closely with psychology teams to ensure the platform aligns with required specifications and user experiences.

DetecSolutions | Bandung, Indonesia Web Developer, Feb 2014 – Nov 2014

 Work together with the existing team to develop SaaS web application.

PT. Neuronworks Indonesia | Bandung, Indonesia Junior Programmer, 2008 - 2013

- Participated in the complete product development lifecycle of successfully launched applications.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to define, design, and implement new features.
- Worked on bug fixing and improving application performance.
- Wrote clean, maintainable, and efficient code in line with software development best practices.

ANDRI RAHMAN HAKIM

PROFILE

A full stack web developer (work on both backend and frontend development) which is passionate build various web application, creating seamless user experiences and visually compelling designs for the web, which resonate with audiences and drive engagement.

SOCIAL

LinkedIn: <u>Andri Rahman Hakim</u>Upwork: <u>Andri Rahman Hakim</u>

• Sribu: Andri Rahman Hakim

• Github: Arhakim

EDUCATION

Politeknik Telkom | Bandung, Indonesia Diploma Of Management Information System, 2010

- Graduate with a score of 3.15
- Specialized in Management Information Systems
- Project: "Library Book Borrowing System Management"

NIIT & Telkom Center | Bandung, Indonesia Associate's Degree of Software Engineering, 2007

- Graduate with a score of 3.05
- Developing an application every semester
- Research and analyze about informatic systems every 3 months.
- Relevant coursework: Typography, App Development, Web Development, SDLC (Software Development Life Cycle)
- Basic Programming Language: C++, Java (J2EE, J2SE and J2ME), SQL, Linux Shell Script, C#, Flash script, HTML, CSS and Javascript.